BRADLEY ROSENFELD

(224) 650-7624 https://bradleyrosenfeld.com thatguy@bradleyrosenfeld.com

Overview

I am a developer who is passionate about web development, good design, and information security. I have over 5 years of experience in designing and developing responsive user interfaces for screens of any size. My objective is to work for an organization that is excited about creating secure, user-friendly web applications.

Education

Taylor University

http://taylor.edu, August, 2012 - May, 2016 B.S. Computer Science - New Media / Systems, 3.77/4.0 GPA, Manga Cum Laude

Awards

Outstanding Systems Graduate, 2016

Taylor University CS&E Department

This award is given to a student who best exemplifies what the Systems program is trying to teach through their outstanding class and project work.

Outstanding Peformance NSA CyberSpring Competition, 2015

National Security Agency
Placed top 30 out of 160+ competitors in a live CTF competition.

Skills

Languages

- C, C++
- PHP, Python, Ruby
- HTML, CSS, Sass, LESS, JavaScript

Tools

- Git, Subversion
- Grunt, NPM, Bower, Unix Tools
- Angular.js, Node.js, jQuery
- Windows, Linux, Mac OS X

Networking

- TCP/IP, DNS, SSH, HTTP, TLS, socket programming
- Apache, Nginx, MySQL

Techniques

- Penetration testing, reverse engineering
- Debugging, Q/A testing
- Agile, scrum

Projects

Visit my GitHub profile (https://github.com/BoringCode) for a list of my open source contributions and projects.

Experience

Sells Group

https://sellsgroup.com, Web Developer

2013 - Present

- Responsible for front-end development on client marketing sites. Worked with team to execute project roadmaps.
- · Built custom e-commerce platform on top of WordPress. Focused on application security from the front-end to the back-end
- Configured development build pipeline on multiple platforms. Set up automatic production deployments. Configured AWS installations.

Floodlight Design

http://floodlight.design, Web Developer

2011 - 2013

- In charge of front-end development. Converted static Photoshop designs into flexible layouts
- $\bullet \ \ Integrated \ static \ templates \ with \ Word Press \ and \ Joomla \ templating \ systems$
- Developed JavaScript for site interactions and API integrations

Highgate Creative

http://highgate-creative.com, Mobile Web Developer

2013 - 2014

- Advised on responsive design best practices. Developed and wrote documentation for an internal responsive web design framework.
- Developed several mobile themes for a custom content management system
- Crafted a jQuery mobile theme for use on a client marketing website